S. D. Jackson Diaries
S. D. Jackson Diaries
1880-1897
Jackson, S. D.
15 v. (SC)
Diaries of a farmer in Oswego County; volumes missing for 1881, 1887 and 1894.
149223
Biographical History
S. D. Jackson (fl. 1880-1897) was an American farmer who lived in Sand Bank (Oswego County), N.Y. during the second half of the 19th century.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The S. D. Jackson Diaries consist of 15 diaries of the Oswego County farmer. The diaries discuss details such as weather conditions, daily activities, and bills owed. Each diary is bound and contains an almanac for the respective year at the front of the volume. With the exception of 1881, 1887, and 1894, which are absent from the collection, there is a single diary for each year.
Arrangement of the Collection
The diaries are arranged chronologically.
Subject and Genre Headings
New York State; Jackson, S. D. -- Diaries.; Farmers -- Diaries.; Oswego County (N.Y.); Diaries.; Farmers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Writings
  - Diaries
    - 1880 (Sc 260, Folder 1)
    - 1882 (Sc 260, Folder 1)
    - 1883 (Sc 260, Folder 1)
    - 1884 (Sc 260, Folder 1)
    - 1885 (Sc 260, Folder 1)
    - 1886 (Sc 260, Folder 1)
    - 1888 (Sc 260, Folder 1)
    - 1889 (Sc 260, Folder 1)
    - 1890 (Sc 260, Folder 2)
    - 1891 (Sc 260, Folder 2)
    - 1892 (Sc 260, Folder 2)
    - 1893 (Sc 260, Folder 2)
    - 1895 (Sc 260, Folder 2)
    - 1896 (Sc 260, Folder 2)
    - 1897 (Sc 260, Folder 2)